<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LASWARCO</string>
    <string name="naigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer </string>
    <string name="naigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer </string>
    <string name="title_activity_testing">TestingActivity</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="paraghraph">
        <b>About LARWASCO</b>
        \n\n
        In a bid to reorganize the State’s water sector for effective service delivery and to encourage competitive, the Commission was created  through the Water Sector Law 2004.</string>

    <string name="vision">

        <b>OUR VISION</b>\n\n
To achieve a water and waste water sector that ensures the delivery of efficient, qualitative and sustainable water supply and waste water management service for present and future inhabitants of the state.</string>

    <string name="mandate">

        <b>OUR MANDATE</b>\n\n
Ensure water supply and wastewater management services are properly carried out in Lagos State.
\n\n
Ensure operators in the sector secure reasonable return on investment to finance the proper delivery of these services and promote sustainability.</string>


    <string name="borehole_permit"><b>Borehole Permit</b>
\n\n
        As part of its functions, LASWARCO regulates , monitor, control abstraction, consumption, distribution, supply, quality of service, sale and use of water and
        tariff and charges payable to ensure financial stability of the water sector and regulate allowable returns to the operator.</string>

    <string name="borehole_drillers_license"><b>Borehole Drillers License </b>
        \n\n
    To control and regulate the placement and drilling of boreholes in line with the best international standard and according to the Lagos State standard procedure. </string>
    <string name="water_and_wastewater_treatment_plant_certification"><b>Water and Wastewater Treatment Plant Certification</b> \n\n
We provide water and wastewater treatment plant certification for businesses that are into industrial use of water and wastewater services</string>
    <string name="water_use_audit"><b>Water Use Audit</b> \n\n
Water use audits, like their energy counterparts, are an important first step toward understanding both a facility’s water use and what can be done to reduce it.</string>
    <string name="function"><b>FUNCTIONS OF THE COMMISSION</b>\n\n
The Lagos State Water Regulatory Commission (LASWARCO) was created in a build to have a viable water sector in the year 2004 and commence operation fully in 2012,
        the Water Sector Law 2004) was amended by the Environmental Management and Protection Law 2017.</string>

    <string name="testing"><b>LASWARCO Testing Lab</b>\n\n

Our full equipped laboratory performs a wide range of bacteriological and chemical tests on drinking water supplies, such as drinking water, surface water, groundwater, and sewage water.</string>

</resources>